diablohub.com 2016-05-11

# DiabloHub - Your source for everything Diablo 3

_Last updated March 1st, 2013_

DiabloHub is respects the privacy rights and concerns of all users using this website. To make this notice easy to find, we have made it available on every page of the website.

**Cookies:**   
We send cookies to users accessing the website. Cookies are used to improve the quality of our website, for such things things such as staying logged in your account. We also use Google Analytics to track our website statistics. Google Analytics is a 3rd party tool to measure the activity and and behaviour of vistors to our website 

**The Information We Collect:**   
When registering on the website, we collect the following information:   
Username   
Email address

The username supplied is used to identify you when posting content to our website - An email address is required for all accounts. Your email address will not be publicly displayed on any part of the website, but it will be visible to DiabloHub Admins. 

We allow users to submit optional personal information through the DiabloHub User Control Panel (Settings). This optional information is:  
Name  
Birthday   
Gender   
Location 

If you choose to disclose personally identifying information, please be aware that DiabloHub is a public web site and anyone is able to read your posts, so there is no expectation of privacy for user-generated content. During your usage of this website, our servers record information that your browser sends to our server whenever you visit the Site. The server will log each request with your IP address, date and time, browser version, and the resource requested from the webserver. We use this informationanalyze how users use the DiabloHub website, to in the end provide a better user experience. 

**Information Sharing:**   
None of your personal information is shared with 3rd parties. Any personal data provided is only used to better identify yourself to other users on your user profile page. 

Your email address will be used to reset your password. 

Your IP Address is used to identify you across the website. Should we determine that a problem with the site is being caused by a certain IP address, we can match the IP address in the log files with registered and inn certain cases we may ban a IP Address from accessing our website. 

**Data Security:**   
DiabloHub runs on hosting servers which only a few trusted site staff have access to. Your password and email information is encrypted in the database. 

**Children's Privacy:**   
We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. Children's privacy is a serious matter and we encourage parents to play an active role in their children's online experience at all times. 

**Accessing your Information:**   
You can access all your information through the DiabloHub Settings page. 

**Notification of Changes:**   
If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post any changes on our site and provide a notification through the websites notifcation center so that users will be made aware of what changes have been made to the Privacy Policy, and continued use of DiabloHub shall constitute consent to the changes in the Privacy Policy. 

**Questions? Contact Us**   
If you have any questions about our privacy practices or this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email at contact@diablohub.com
